Greek Meets Greek is a comedy film directed by Nicholas T. Barrows.
Eddie Boland is a scholar of Greek philosophy and is in his study
when the butler interrupts him with a message.
In the next room his sister (Ethel Broadhurst) has her
friends over and are making a lot of noise.
The professor flips and confronts them all and resorts to mocking them
with "you dress like peacocks and dance like turkeys."
The Professor of Greek, played by Eddie Boland.
The Shimmy Teacher, played by Ethel Broadhurst.
Alexander (Greek: Αλέξανδρος, romanized: Aléxandros; 1 August 1893 – 25 October 1920)
was King of Greece from 11 June 1917 until his death on 25 October 1920.
The second son of King Constantine I, Alexander was born in the
summer palace of Tatoi on the outskirts of Athens.
He succeeded his father in 1917, during World War I, after the Entente Powers and the followers of
Eleftherios Venizelos pushed King Constantine and his eldest son, Crown Prince George, into exile.
Having no real political experience, the new king was stripped of his powers by
the Venizelists and effectively imprisoned in his own palace.
Venizelos, as prime minister, was the effective
ruler with the support of the Entente.
Though reduced to the status of a puppet king, Alexander supported Greek
troops during their war against the Ottoman Empire and Bulgaria.
Under his reign, the territorial extent of Greece considerably increased, following the victory of the Entente and
their Allies in the First World War and the early stages of the Greco-Turkish War of 1919–1922.
Alexander controversially married the commoner Aspasia Manos in 1919, provoking a
major scandal that forced the couple to leave Greece for several months.
Soon after returning to Greece with his wife, Alexander was bitten by a
domestic Barbary macaque and died aged 27 of sepsis.
The sudden death of the sovereign led to questions over the monarchy's
survival and contributed to the fall of the Venizelist regime.
After a general election and a referendum,
Constantine I was restored to the throne.
The tone is lighthearted.